publicitywires.com 2009-06-12

# PublicityWires.com: Privacy Policy

PublicityWires.com website, owned and operated by PublicityWires (collectively referred to as "PublicityWires", "PublicityWires.com", "we", "our" or "us"), is a public relations services portal, a service provider which :- 

\- posts and/or distributes press releases/media requests on behalf of its User; and   
\- posts public relations firms listing on behalf of its User. 

Any person who accesses the PublicityWires.com website and submits personal data is User of the website (collectively referred to as "you", "your" or "user"). You are welcome to discover all the Information on the PublicityWires.com and can freely explore the website largely without having to reveal any personal data. 

On occasion, however, it may be necessary for the PublicityWires.com to gather information on you for a specific purpose. PublicityWires.com may collect two types of information from you: personal data you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and the PublicityWires.com website user information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse the PublicityWires.com website. 

This statement created by PublicityWires.com is to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering methods and dissemination practices for the PublicityWires.com. PublicityWires.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other linked sites.

1./ Use of your Personal Information

When you post or submit press releases for distribution through PublicityWires.com, such press releases and personal information therein contained to its media contact profile or in the forms will be on distribution. By submitting press releases and personal information in the requisite forms, You certify that all information provided to the PublicityWires.com is true and correct and indicates your consent with this policy. 

The PublicityWires.com collects your contact information (such as an e-mail address or contact numbers, etc) and demographic information (for instance, city and/or country of residence, types of company or areas/topics/industry of interested or related to the User, etc). This information is used by PublicityWires.com to further our statutory objectives. Failure to provide such information may result in our being unable to provide you with our services including access to the PublicityWires.com website. Your contact information from the forms is used to send promotional materials and information required to you. You may "opt-out" of receiving future promotional mailings. If data collected is to be displayed at a later date, due care will be given to keep it anonymous and you will be advised in advance. Demographic information is used for our research requirements and to tailor your experience at our site, showing content of interested, and displaying the content according to your preferences. We may share with our advertisers / sponsors such information on an aggregate basis. 

PublicityWires.com server software records your domain name and computer, when you visit the website. We track the pages your visits. We do these so that we can measure traffic, gauge the popularity of various parts of the PublicityWires.com, gain general knowledge about our users and compile aggregated statistics. 

If you choose to purchase products or services from us, you may need to give personal data and authorize us to obtain information from various credit services. For instance, you may need to provide the following information:-   
\- Name on credit card   
\- Credit card number and expiry date   
\- Bank account details 

If you choose to correspond further with us through email, PublicityWires.com may retain the content of the email messages together with the email address and our responses. PublicityWires.com provides the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone. 

All data collected by the PublicityWires.com is used only for the purposes indicated above. PublicityWires.com will not share User personal information with any third parties except under the following circumstances: 

(a) On a confidential basis to agents, advisers, auditors or service providers PublicityWires.com use in the ordinary course of our business, such as for data management and distribution of our promotional materials, and/or in connection with our operations.   
(b) As we may be required to do so by laws.   
(c) As you indicated your consent to receive promotional materials from third parties.   
(d) Banks and other financial institutions in connection with the collection of payments.   
(e) Any actual or proposed transferee of our business or the PublictiyWires.com website or any part of our business or PublicityWires.com website or participant in our operations. 

User should note that the privacy protection as set out in this Privacy Policy does not apply to personal data which is passed to third parties, and PublicityWires.com is not responsible for the protection of your personal data or lack thereof by such third parties. 

2./ Cookies

PublicityWires.com will use User's IP address to assist in diagnosing problems with our server, and to administer our Website. User's IP address is used to identify you and to gather broad demographic information. PublicityWires.com uses cookies to deliver content specific to User's interests. 

You can set your browsers in order to be notified when receive a cookie, offering the opportunity to decide whether to accept or not. PublicityWires.com uses various types of forms for User to request information and services and to send e-mail messages of preferred pages. 

From time to time you may notice offers or advertisements from other companies on the PublicityWires.com website. We endeavour to take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford privacy protections to their customers. However, we do not make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies. You may opt-out of sharing your personal data with such affiliates by choosing not to use their service or content. 

3./ Security for Data

The PublicityWires.com will take reasonable measure/steps to ensure that all information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and stored in a secure environment accessed only by authorized persons. However, PublicityWires.com gives no warranty against hacking into the data by any third parties or any unauthorized access to the date by anyone. All information collect is used to notify User about updates to our service and inform User of special events organised by PublicityWires.com or its partners. PublicityWires.com will not share with other organizations for commercial or non-commercial purposes. 

All User's credit card details are encrypted for transmission over the Internet (using 128-bit SSL encryption). 

In the events of unauthorized use of your personal credit card occurs as a result of sending the credit card number to the PublicityWires.com as part of your purchase, PublicityWires.com will reimburse the actual amount (if any) your credit card issuer requires you to bear for unauthorized use, up to a maximum US$10, provided you present evidence that you have given written notice to your credit card issuer as soon as you become aware of the unauthorized use, and were required to and have paid your credit card issuer for the particular instance of unauthorized use. You will not be entitled to claim such reimbursement if the unauthorized use was due to your default, negligence or omission. PublicityWires.com reserves the rights to deny any claims and its decision shall be final. 

4./ Rights Under the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance

This Privacy Policy is developed according to the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance of the Laws of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region of The People's Republic of China. This Ordinance provides data subjects with rights to ascertain whether the PublicityWires.com holds personal data relating to them, to correct any data that is inaccurate and to obtain a copy of that data. PublicityWires.com may charge a reasonable fee for processing any data access request.

5./ Updating User Profile / Opt-out

You can have access to your account profile to update or correct your personal information at your sole discretion. 

You also can opt-out from receiving promotion materials from the PublicityWires.com and/or its partners. Should you no longer wish to receive updates from the PublicityWires.com developments, activities and promotions, you can delete your information from our data at any time. 

Should you have further questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the use and the practices of this Website, please contact [webmaster@publicitywires.com](mailto:webmaster@publicitywires.com). We will process your request within 30 working days. 

6./ Use of Personal Data in Legal Procedures

If it becomes necessary that we take legal action against you for any reason whatsoever including copyright infringement, you expressly agree that the personal data provided by you can be relied upon in identifying and taking action against you.

7./ About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. 

We retain personal data so long as the data is still required for the purposes mentioned above. Your personal data is stored on our server in Hong Kong and is accessible only to authorized employees. We reserve the right to retain copies indefinitely for our archives. 

8./ About Other Websites Linked to PublicityWires.com website

PublicityWires.com website contains links to other sites and occasionally allows other sites to be co-branded with the Publicitywires.com. When you use a link to go from PublicityWires.com to another Website or when you use a co-branded website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites that have a link to the PublicityWires.com, is subject to that website's own rules and policies which may differ from that of the PublicityWires.com. 

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website nor the information or content contained therein. 

9./ Your Consent

By using the PublicityWires.com website, you consent to our collection and use of your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy.

10./ Miscellaneous

\- The headings in these terms are for convenience only and do not affect interpretation.   
\- This Privacy Policy is subject to change without prior or separate notification. User is recommended to check it out on our Website on a regular basis. 

Updated 8 August, 2007.
